digitalcombatsimulator.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy and cookie policy

## Introduction

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy and Cookie Policy ("Policy") describes how we treat information that you provide to us or that we collect about you.

By personal data, we refer to data that relates to you as an identified or identifiable person. Personal data include your name, your address, your telephone number, your e-mail address, your age, your gender and your game preferences, a part of your credit card number. Anonymous information, which we are not in a position to relate to you, does not qualify as personal data.

We may collect personal data as well as other information when you use the following services:

Our websites, including [digitalcombatsimulator.com](https://www.digitalcombatsimulator.com/), [digitalcombatsimulator.ch](http://www.digitalcombatsimulator.ch/), [digitalcombatsimulator.ru](http://www.digitalcombatsimulator.ru/), [dcs-world.com](http://dcs-world.com/), [dcs-world.ch](http://dcs-world.ch/), [dcs-world.cn](http://dcs-world.cn/), [dcs-world.ru](http://dcs-world.ru/), [dcs.world](http://dcs.world/) and any other Eagle Dynamics SA or The Fighter Collection Ltd sites on which this Policy is posted (the "Sites").

Your creation and use of a DCS World account on any of the Sites (an "Account"). For more information on Accounts and how to create an Account please see our Terms of Service.

Your use of any of PC games including, but not limited to, "DCS World", additional modules, campaigns and terrains (the "Games" or individually a "Game"). Your use of each Game will be subject to the End User License Agreement (the "EULA") in respect of that Game. You can read the EULA for our Games during the purchase process on our Sites or in the Game. Your use of any of the Games Forums we operate as part of the Game will be subject to the rules and guidelines applicable to the Games Forums (the "Forum Rules"). The Forum Rules are set out at <https://forums.eagle.ru/rules.php#en> and constitute a part of Terms of Service.

In this Policy we refer to the Sites, the Account and the Games together as the "Services".

Please read this Policy carefully. By use of any of the Services, you accept the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not attempt to use the Services. By accepting this Policy, you signify your consent to the collection and other processing of your personal data in accordance with and for the purposes set out in this Policy.

## Information we collect

The information we collect depends on what products you use and how you use them. The controller of the personal information collected is Eagle Dynamics SA, Av. de Florimont 3, 1006 Lausanne, Switzerland.

We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal data and other information you provide to us, or we collect about you, in accordance with applicable privacy and personal data protection laws.

When ordering or registering on our Sites, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or other details to help you with your experience.

## How we collect information

We collect some information from you when you provide it to us directly, such as via an online form or when you talk with our technical support team.

## How we use your information

We use your personal and non-personal information in the following ways to:

  * Operate, improve, and develop our games and services;
  * Populate online leaderboards and enable online matchmaking;
  * Facilitate sharing on social networks;
  * Set up loyalty programs;
  * Identify, fix, and troubleshoot bugs and service errors;
  * Provide software updates;
  * Activate or authenticate your games and save game progress and stats;
  * Help keep our services safe and fair, resolve disputes, investigate and help curb fraud and illegal behavior, comply with the law, and to enforce our agreements and policies;
  * Help identify and troubleshoot problems with your account or games;
  * Communicate with you and respond to your specific requests or questions;
  * Manage and send you confirmations and important information about your account, products, purchases, subscriptions, and warranties.
  * Present offers and/or information relating to games you might like.

## How we protect your personal information

Security of our players' information is a priority at The Fighter Collection Ltd and Eagle Dynamics SA, and we take a range of measures to help protect it, including encryption of sensitive financial information. Even so, no security measure is 100% perfect. This means we cannot guarantee the security of your information and do not assume any responsibility for the unauthorized use or access to your information under our control.

## Cookies and similar technologies

Cookies are small text files stored on your Internet browser. We use cookies and similar technologies to help us understand things like what web pages, features or ads you view and what games you play. This information helps us keep track of your shopping cart, measure the effectiveness of our advertising, make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly and otherwise help enhance your user experience. You can disable cookies, limit the types of cookies you allow, or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. Please refer to http://www.allaboutcookies.org or the guidance provided by your individual web browser if you'd like help in managing your cookie preferences.

We use other technologies for similar purposes as a cookie. We use pixels or clear GIFs to collect information about your use of our products and your response to our marketing emails. We use Internet log files (which contain technical data such as your IP address) to monitor traffic on our products, troubleshoot technical problems, detect and prevent fraud and enforce our User Agreement. Other examples include HTML 5 cookies, Silverlight Application Storage, device fingerprints and "flash cookies." If you want to remove flash cookies or prevent them from being placed, adjust your preferences in the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html. We currently do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. We may adopt a DNT standard if one is established. In the meantime, you may opt out of certain types of tracking, including certain analytics and tailored advertising by changing your cookie settings.

## Changes to our Policy

We may update this policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of our products means you accept the changes. Once you accept this policy, we will not enforce future changes we deem in good faith to be material absent your express agreement to the changed terms. If you are asked to affirmatively accept material changes to this policy and you decline to do so, you may not be able to continue to use the product provided. The latest version of this Policy will always be available on the Sites.

## Questions and comments

If you have a complaint or question about this policy, you may contact us at <https://www.digitalcombatsimulator.com/en/support/>.

When you visit this website, you accept the following provisions and conditions without reservation.
